Privacy Policy
==============

Updated April 26, 2023

iMobie is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We (iMobie) do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

This Privacy Policy also explains what information we collect about you and why, what we do with that information, and how we handle that information. We’ll also explain what rights you have with respect to the information.

#### 1\. Applicability of This Policy

This Policy Privacy applies to all iMobie’s websites (collectively, the “Websites”), desktop and mobile applications (collectively, the “Products”), services, and other interactions (e.g., customer service inquiries, user conferences, etc.) you may have with iMobie. If you do not agree with the terms, do not access or use the Products, Websites or any other aspect of iMobie’s business.

#### 2\. What Information We Collect

When you visit iMobie Websites, place an order on our Websites or on the Products, use our applications, submit your comments or feedback to us, contact customer support, or other interactions related to iMobie, we may collect your personal information to complete transactions, provide better services to you. What specific information we may collect is below:

(1) When you visit our Websites:

(a) We may collect information about how you visit our Websites (including the webpage that led you to a iMobie.  
Websites, the search terms entered into a search engine which led you to a iMobie Websites).  
(b) Your operations and clicks to our Websites.  
(c) Date and time of the visit and the duration of use of the Websites.  

(2) When you place an order on our Websites or the Products:

Your personal information including full name, email address, country, language, mailing address, phone number, postal code, credit card number will be required, to complete transactions.

(3) When you use our Products:

We have different kinds of Products and different Products may collect different data. Generally, we may collect the data below if you use our Products.

(a) Your product serial number.  
(b) We collect information about the products which you use and how you use them, including but not limited to launch data, feature usage, page clicks, sign-in information, etc.  
(c) Your local device information, including but not limited to your device information, device hardware, operating system, other software on your system, username, your iMobie ID, location, IP address, operating log information, the size and format of the files you are working with.  
(d) Crash information. If you meet a crash problem, we will submit the crash information of the system feedback to the tracking information.  
(e) iMobie SyncTrans uses OAuth authentication to configure cloud storage services for the application on your behalf, which may include viewing and managing your Google cloud service storage files such as photo albums, media libraries, shared albums, etc. SyncTrans does not store any of your files. SyncTrans only transfers and processes information based on requests from valid users who access or transfer files.  

(4) When you use our App(eg. AnyMiro):

Among the types of Personal Data that our Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are Camera permission; Audio recording permission; Location permission; Background service permission.

(a) Camera permission: Scan the QR code to process the computer information, then connect the device to the computer and mirror.  
(b) Audio recording permission: Process the built-in speaker sound source and mirror to the computer software.  
(c) Location permission: Use UDP scanning of surrounding devices to process computer information. Display the Wifi name to ensure that the user is on the same network as the computer.  
(d) Background service permission: Ensure the stability of the connection when mirroring.

(5) When you submit content to us:

When you submit a ticket to us for customer support, we may collect your information including your name, email address, age group, product name, and the content of messages to offer you better services.

#### 3\. How Do We Process the Collected Information

#### 3.1 How Do We Use Your Personal Information

We may use your personal information for the purposes below:

(a) For verifying your identification to complete an order or provide appropriate services.  
(b) For Internal statistical and analytical purposes. Analyze your use of our Websites and Products to better.  
understand how they are being used, so we can improve our services and the user experience, engage and retain users.  
(c) For investigation to prevent security issues, fraud and abuse.  
(d) Respond to any requirements and offer technical support.  
(e) Use the comments (with your relevant information) you post for marketing purposes in order for others to better understand and use our products.  
(f) For the requirements of applicable laws, legal processes or regulations.  
(g) For the purposes of refund management.  
(h) The subscription to iMobie’s newsletters and the related provision of personal data is made on a voluntary basis so that the processing of the collected personal data relies on your consent.  
(i) Keep you informed with iMobie’s latest updates. We may send technical and services support, or other administrative emails, billing reminders messages, security announcements, etc. We may also contact you to inform you about changes about our Websites, Products, or services,such as iMobie newsletters, new product features, promotional offers, or periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. You may also occasionally receive product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you about other products or services available from iMobie and its affiliates. You have full freedom to stop receiving from us any time.  

#### 3.2 How Do We Save & Protect the Collected Information

iMobie respects and protects your personal information strictly. We apply appropriate physical, management, and technical measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, modification, damage, or loss. We will not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. iMobie will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

We may suspend your use of all or part of the services without notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security. If you believe that information you provided to us is no longer secure, please notify us immediately using the contact information provided below.

We keep your personal data only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes and as permitted by applicable law. In practice, this means that we delete or anonymize your account after three (3) years of continuous inactivity unless we must keep it to comply with applicable law; because an issue, claim or dispute has not yet been resolved; or the information must be kept for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud prevention and enhancing users' safety and security. Please note that, although our systems are designed to carry out data deletion processes, we cannot promise that deletion will occur within a specific timeframe due to technical constraints.

#### 3.3 Disclosure of Your Personal Information

iMobie may share or disclose your personal information to third parties to the extent described below and not beyond.

At times iMobie may make certain personal information available to third-party credit card processors to fulfill customer orders and deliver products. Such as Paddle, Stripe, MyCommerce, Share-it and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transactions.

We may also share your personal information with companies that help us to run our business by processing personal information on behalf of us for the purposes identified above. Such companies include email delivery service providers which can help us deliver promotion emails to you, server companies we hire to provide service to you, social medias, third party online forums, and other marketing platforms and service providers.

We may also access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on iMobie; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of iMobie (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of iMobie services or members of the public.

iMobie does not rent or sell your Personal Information for commercial purposes.

#### 4\. Newsletters and Advertising Emails

iMobie may contact you to inform you about new product announcements, software updates, and special offers, promotional newsletters, etc. We also may want to contact you with information about products and services from our business partners.

We only send marketing communications to users with your prior consent. You have the right to unsubscribe at any time.

#### 5\. Cookies and Tracking Tools

iMobie may use third-party cookie and trace tools (such as AdWords, Bing, Disqus, Facebook, FireBase, Google Analytics, Hotjar, LinkedIn) to track how you use information websites and products, such websites use data and product use data May be sent and stored in a third-party server located outside the EU. Such third-party cookies and tracking tools may send trace data or analysis reports to iMobie for the purpose of the above purposes. Most third-party cookies and tracking tools handle your personal data in an anonymous manner. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer.

Most Web browsers accept cookies by default, but if you choose not to accept them, you can simply change your browser settings to disable it. If you decline to accept cookies, you may not receive the full benefits that our website has to offer. Here are some guides on how to delete or disable cookies on your browser:  
for Safari users: [how to delete and disable on Safari](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265)  
for Chrome users: [how to delete and disable on Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647)  
for IE users: [how to delete and disable on Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies)  
for Firefox users: [how to delete and disable on Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)  
for Opera users: [how to delete and disable on Opera](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/)  
for Edge users: [how to delete and disable on Microsoft Edge](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy)

#### 6\. Third Party Data

iMobie may receive data about Website visitors, marketing campaigns and other matters related to our business from affiliates and subsidiaries, our partners or others that we use to make our own information better or more useful. This data may be combined with Other Information we collect and might include aggregate level data, such as which IP addresses correspond to zip codes or countries. Or it might be more specific: for example, how well an online marketing or email campaign performed.

#### 7\. Your Rights At iMobie

You may [contact us](mailto:contact@imobie.com) to correct, amend, or delete your personal information, your forum account, newsletter subscriptions, or your support tickets, etc. However, some information may remain in archived/backup copies to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. You also have the rights to:

(a) be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how iMobie collects and uses your personal data.  
(b) lodge an objection to the processing of your personal data at any time, on grounds relating to your particular situation.  
(c) obtain access to your personal data (if iMobie is processing it), and other certain information (similar to that provided in this privacy policy).  
(d) ‘block’ or suppress further use of its personal data under certain circumstances.

#### 8\. Updates to This Privacy Policy

iMobie may modify and update this Privacy Policy from time to time, to keep pace with changes in our Websites, Products, and Services, our business, and laws applicable to us and you. We will, however, always maintain our commitment to respect your privacy. We will notify you of any material changes that impact your rights under this Policy by email (to your most recently provided email address) or post any other revisions to this Policy, along with their effective date, in an easy-to-find area of the Websites, so we recommend that you periodically check back here to stay informed of any changes. Please note that your continued use of iMobie after any change means that you agree with, and consent to be bound by, the new Policy. If you disagree with any changes in this Policy and do not wish your information to be subject to it, you will need to stop using the Websites and/or Products or other services.

#### 9\. Contact iMobie

If after reading this statement, you have any questions about iMobie’s privacy policy, please submit your questions to  

#### 10\. YouTube Privacy Policy

#### 10.1 Privacy when uploading to YouTube

When uploading contents to YouTube through iMobie software (e.g AnyMirror), Google's privacy policy applies to media uploaded to YouTube. You can view the Google privacy policy here:  

#### 10.2 Revoking access to YouTube Data

You could revoke the access of iMobie software (e.g AnyMirror) to YouTube at any time via the Google security settings page at:
